axcessmypics.com 2006-12-06

# Alltel.com Privacy Statement

Home | **Privacy Statement**

Download a PDF of our Privacy Statement.

We limit the information collected about you to what is needed for conducting business and offering products and services that might be of interest to you. You may choose to provide individually identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) to Alltel in a number of ways through our Web site — by ordering a service from us, sending us e-mail, registering to receive news or public information or applying for a job.

**We do not:**

  * Collect individually identifiable information from you unless you provide it to us.
  * Sell the names and addresses of visitors to our site to unaffiliated suppliers, without providing information on that disclosure where the individually identifiable information is collected.

**We do:**

  * Use security techniques designed to protect customers' information from unauthorized access. See Information Security below. 
  * Collect, maintain and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customers' needs (e.g. customer care or new products or services).
  * Honor customers' requests to remove their names from our telephone or mail solicitation lists using reasonable efforts to delete the information from existing files. Just contact us.
  * When undertaking projects with other companies, provide access to customer information with an understanding that our business partners will also treat the information with respect for privacy concerns.

In addition to individually identifiable information, we may collect information automatically when a visitor enters an Alltel site, such as the domain name, browser, the type of computer operating system, information about the Web page from which the visitor linked to the site, and time spent on different pages within the site. We may use this information to evaluate and improve the site, and may share the information with business partners and others.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique Alltel.com User ID. We use cookies to deliver Web content specific to your interests and to control access to your personal shopping cart after your initial entry. The cookie permits the server to recall information from your previous shopping trip, should you decide to think about your purchase or talk it over with your spouse. A cookie is not used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. With most browsers, you can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on Alltel.com.

**Information Security**  
We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. When you place an order, the information you submit is encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Value Added**  
Because we appreciate the trust you have placed in us, we continually look for ways to enhance that business relationship. So from time to time, we may let you know about a product or service. Using the information you have provided to us, we strive to limit our offers to those we think you would appreciate receiving. We want every contact you have with us to be a positive experience. So if you would prefer not to receive these value-added services, offers and opportunities, just contact us.

**Children**  
Children should consult with their parents or guardian before furnishing any data to us. We believe that parents should supervise their children's on-line activities and may consider using one of a number of available parental control tools that provide a child-friendly, on-line environment and can prevent children from disclosing individually identifiable information without parental consent. If a child has provided individually identifiable information without the consent of a parent or guardian, that parent or guardian should just contact us to request that the information be deleted from our records. Get more information about parental controls.

**Links**  
Alltel is not responsible for content or privacy policies of other sites. You should keep this in mind when accessing sites through links on Alltel's Web site.

**Updates**  
As with all Alltel sites, we will constantly strive to improve the services we may offer, and may update this privacy statement from time to time in connection with that effort. We reserve the right to expand our capabilities for information collection and use, and may change our policies along with this privacy statement at any time.
